

Jorge Luis Hernández Dueñas

Software Engineer

## CONTACTS

- jorgelhd94@gmail.com
- +53 56163564
- Havana, Cuba
- https://jorgelhd94.github.io/portfolio/

Never stop learning and always make it fun

## PROFILE

Computer engineer with a strong passion and great interest in programming, software development, and the technology world in general. As a full stack developer with experience in JavaScript, Typescript, and Python, my goal is to help bring your business to the next level through the creation of high-quality software development tool-based applications and websites.

## TECHNICAL SKILLS

PROGRAMMING JavaScript (ES6 +), Python, LANGUAGES Typescript, CSS3, HTML5

FRAMEWORKS AND ReactJS, NextJS, Django, NodeJS, LIBRARIES NestJS, VueJS, TailwindCSS,

Wordpress, Woocommerce

OPERATING Windows, Linux SYSTEMS

DATABASES SQL, MySQL, PostgreSql, SQLite

CVS AND GIT, Github, Gitlab REPOSITORIES

OTHER TOOLS Docker, Google Cloud, Digital Ocean,

Firebase, Supabase

## PROFILE SUMMARY

WORKING EXPERIENCE 5 years

**S** EDUCATION

Computer Engineering, University of Ciego de Avila

LANGUAGES

Spanish: Native

English: C1 - Advanced

**EF SET Certificate** 

## SOFT SKILLS

- Teamwork
- Effective communication
- Problem solving
- Adaptability
- Time management

## SOCIAL

in Jorge Luis Hernández Dueñas

jorgelhd94

## WORKING EXPERIENCE

## 2019-Today Freelancer Projects

Projects:
<ul> <li>Mercadeo: Marketplace</li> <li>Team: 1 - All positions</li> <li>Main Technologies: NextJs, Supabase</li> </ul>
<ul> <li>Altintin: Marketplace</li> <li>Team: 3 - All positions</li> <li>Main Technologies: NextJs, Django Rest Api</li> </ul>
<ul> <li>AITO: Business Website</li> <li>Team: 1 - Main developer, Testing and Deploy</li> <li>Main Technologies: Wordpress</li> </ul>
<ul> <li>Miimi: Toys Store</li> <li>Team: 3 - Main developer, Testing and Deploy</li> <li>Main Technologies: Woocommerce, Elementor</li> </ul>
<ul> <li>SunFood: Business Website</li> <li>Team: 1 - All positions</li> <li>Main Technologies: Wordpress, Elementor</li> </ul>
<ul> <li>Swiss Cuban Charm: Official Website</li> <li>Team: 3 - Frontend Developer</li> <li>Main Technologies: VueJs</li> </ul>
<ul> <li>☐ Gesmaster: Management of University Master's Courses</li> <li>☐ Team: 1 - All positions</li> <li>☐ Main Technologies: ReactJs, Python</li> </ul>
<ul> <li>University Website: Official website of the University of Ciego de Ávil</li> <li>Team: 1 - All positions</li> <li>Main Technologies: Wordpress</li> </ul>
<ul> <li>NiceQR: Nice QRCode Generator</li> <li>Team: 1 - All positions</li> <li>Main Technologies: ReactJs</li> </ul>
<ul> <li>Auto Parts Management: WebApp for a private company</li> <li>Team: 2 - All positions</li> <li>Main Technologies: VueJs, Python</li> </ul>

### WORKING EXPERIENCE

#### 2021-2022 **EICMA**

- Projects:
  - ☐ Invoice Management System: Manage billing for services
    - Team: 2 All positions
    - Main Technologies: VueJs, Python
  - Institutional Websites: Websites for companies in the agricultural sector
    - Team: 3 Designer and Developer
    - Main Technologies: Wordpress

#### 2018-2021 University of Ciego de Avila

- Projects:
  - ☐ Horus MB (Thesis): Fixed asset management
    - Team: 1 All positions
    - Main Technologies: Android, VueJs, Python
  - ☐ **DataCovid**: (Covid-19) Management of reports and hospital admissions
    - Team: 2 All positions
    - Main Technologies: VueJS, Python
  - Institutional Websites: Websites for companies in the agricultural sector
    - Team: 2 All positions
    - Main Technologies: Wordpress
  - ☐ **FMC and University Apps**: Hibrid Android Apps for share important information
    - Team: 1 All positions
    - Main Technologies: Android, HTML, CSS

# EDUCATION

2014-2019	University of Ciego de Avila, Computer Engineer		
	■ Kno	wledges:	
		C#, Algorithms, Data Structures: 2014-2016 PHP, JavaScript, ES6+, HTML, CSS, Scrum: 2016-2017 VueJs, Python, Java (Android), Python: 2017-2019	
	Cour	rses:	
		Desktop Development: 2014-2016 Web and mobile development: 2016-2019	
2009-2012	Rafael Morales Polytechnic, IT Technician		
	■ Kn	nowledges:	

C++: 2009-2010

☐ PHP, HTML, CSS: 2010-2012